// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the below is valid way to instantiate an array in java?",
    answer: "int myArray [] = {1, 3, 5};",
    options: [
      "int myArray [] = {1, 3, 5};",
      "int myArray [] [] = {1,2,3,4};",
      "int [] myArray = (5, 4, 3);",
      "int [] myArray = {“1”, “2”, “3”};"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Select all the core concepts of OOPS.",
    answer: "All of the Above",
    options: [
      "Abstraction",
      "nheritance",
      "Polymorphism",
      "All of the Above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following statements are true for inheritance in Java?",
    answer: "We can't extend Final classes in java",
    options: [
      "The 'extend' keyword is used to extend a class in java",
      "You can extend multiple classes in java",
      "Private members of the superclass are accessible to the subclass",
      "We can't extend Final classes in java"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the below are unchecked exceptions in java?",
    answer: "All of the Above",
    options: [
      "RuntimeException",
      "ClassCastException",
      "NullPointerException",
      "All of the Above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What will be the output of the below program? public class Test {public static void main(String[] args) { char c = 65; System.out.println('c = ' + c);}",
    answer: "Prints 'c = A'",
    options: [
      "Compile Time Error",
      "Prints 'c = A'",
      "Runtime Error",
      "Prints 'c = 65'"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: " Which of the below are reserved keyword in Java?",
    answer: "goto,int",
    options: [
      "array",
      "goto",
      "goto,int",
      "array,int",
      "int"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Methods such as reverse, shuffle are offered in:",
    answer: "Collection",
    options: [
      "Object",
      "Collection",
      "Collections",
      "Apache Commons Collections"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "java.util.Collections is a:",
    answer: "Class",
    options: [
      "Class",
      "Interface",
      "Object",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "The root interface of Java collection framework hierarchy is ?",
    answer: "List/Set",
    options: [
      "Collection",
      "Root",
      " Collections",
      "List/Set"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is the extension of compiled java classes?",
    answer: ".java",
    options: [
      ".txt",
      ".js",
      ".java",
      ".javac"
    ]
  }
];